# Luke Hopkirk

in LinkedIn

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Otago,

BSc, Computer Science Major, Information Science Minor Graduating In 2024

Feb 2022 - present Dunedin, New Zealand

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **Deliver Easy,** Delivery Driver

Nov 2021 - Feb 2023

While working for Deliver Easy, I was faced with many situations, such as a rush hour period, where I had to manage my time in order to get deliveries done on time. If there was a mistake with a customer's order or something went wrong, I would have to do my best to communicate with Deliver Easy in order to get the best outcome for the customer.

## Kapiti New World, Grocery Assistant

Nov 2019 - Nov 2021 | Kapti

New World provided me with a variety of tasks and responsibilities including stocking shelves, making sure products are organized in the storeroom, assisting customers at the bakery and deli when unstaffed, cleaning up and closing the deli, and assisting customers in finding products around the store.

#### **SKILLS**

**Programming languages** (Java, Python (Pandas, NumPy, scikit-learn, Matplotlib, Seaborn), R, SQL (MySQL, PostgreSQL), C, Javascript, HTML/CSS),

**Technologies / Frameworks:** (Node.js, Docker, React, JUnit, Bash, Unity), **Tools** (Gitlab, Github)

## **PROFILE**

I have studied over the past two years at the University of Otago in order to further my knowledge in the field of computer science. While studying, group projects have helped me gain experience working as a team to produce a certain task. During these projects, we have encountered many real-world issues such as people leaving our group during the project and not having a replacement, as well as strict deadlines on tasks in order to get the final product released on time.

## **PROJECTS**

## **A.N.D.I.E,** University Of Otago

A.N.D.I.E was an image editor to which, as a group, we had to add features to an existing image editor given to us. There was a variety of additions we had to make such as different language support, resizing and cropping of images, rotation of images, undo and redo, keyboard shortcuts, and more. A.N.D.I.E was the first group project I was a part of, and we had to manage our time efficiently as well as communicate well in order to get it finished by the deadline, as two of our group members out of the original 5 had left the university or never showed up to the course. Because of this, we had a lot more pressure than other groups to get the project done, but with good communication between team members, we were able to get it done.

## **Dungeon Rage,** *University Of Otago ⊗*

Dungeon Rage was a 2D dungeon crawler game developed by 4 of us during a 6-week summer school paper. It was all our first time using Unity, and developing a game while trying to learn how Unity works was a good challenge, which ended up being very rewarding in the end. Managing time and having weekly deadlines was crucial during this project, as we had a short timeframe to complete it. However, I believe that we produced a good-looking, polished game that I was proud to show off.